[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "kana": "あ",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["a", "ne", "yu", "wo"],
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "kana": "い",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["yo", "i", "ya", "fu"],
    "answer": "i"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "kana": "う",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["re", "u", "ho", "a"],
    "answer": "u"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "kana": "え",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["ko", "ni", "e", "ta"],
    "answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "kana": "お",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["o", "to", "ha", "no"],
    "answer": "o"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "kana": "か",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["he", "i", "ka", "ku"],
    "answer": "ka"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "kana": "き",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["fu", "tsu", "ki", "u"],
    "answer": "ki"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "kana": "く",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["shi", "wo", "ku", "yo"],
    "answer": "ku"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "kana": "け",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["ri", "ke", "ro", "to"],
    "answer": "ke"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "kana": "こ",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["tsu", "ku", "ko", "na"],
    "answer": "ko"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "kana": "さ",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["so", "se", "chi", "sa"],
    "answer": "sa"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "kana": "し",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["no", "ku", "sa", "shi"],
    "answer": "shi"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "kana": "す",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["te", "mi", "nu", "su"],
    "answer": "su"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "kana": "せ",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["se", "he", "no", "ku"],
    "answer": "se"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "kana": "そ",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["ra", "ne", "so", "a"],
    "answer": "so"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "kana": "た",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["he", "ta", "ka", "te"],
    "answer": "ta"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "kana": "ち",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["sa", "ma", "wo", "chi"],
    "answer": "chi"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "kana": "つ",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["sa", "ko", "tsu", "su"],
    "answer": "tsu"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "kana": "て",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["te", "ro", "me", "shi"],
    "answer": "te"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "kana": "と",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["fu", "ko", "to", "u"],
    "answer": "to"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "kana": "な",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["fu", "mi", "na", "he"],
    "answer": "na"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "kana": "に",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["wa", "ni", "no", "he"],
    "answer": "ni"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "kana": "ぬ",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["o", "nu", "ma", "ko"],
    "answer": "nu"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "kana": "ね",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["so", "he", "ne", "ma"],
    "answer": "ne"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "kana": "の",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["no", "me", "se", "ra"],
    "answer": "no"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "kana": "は",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["ru", "shi", "ro", "ha"],
    "answer": "ha"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "kana": "ひ",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["hi", "fu", "se", "to"],
    "answer": "hi"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "kana": "ふ",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["a", "ku", "u", "fu"],
    "answer": "fu"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "kana": "へ",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["ni", "yo", "ri", "he"],
    "answer": "he"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "kana": "ほ",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["su", "ka", "a", "ho"],
    "answer": "ho"
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "kana": "ま",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["ko", "ma", "ro", "yo"],
    "answer": "ma"
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "kana": "み",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["te", "mi", "na", "ni"],
    "answer": "mi"
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "kana": "む",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["shi", "o", "mu", "fu"],
    "answer": "mu"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "kana": "め",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["wo", "ru", "no", "me"],
    "answer": "me"
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "kana": "も",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["ni", "mo", "ya", "ta"],
    "answer": "mo"
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "kana": "や",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["no", "ru", "ya", "shi"],
    "answer": "ya"
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "kana": "ゆ",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["he", "u", "yu", "ra"],
    "answer": "yu"
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "kana": "よ",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["yo", "wo", "ku", "ri"],
    "answer": "yo"
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "kana": "ら",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["so", "se", "ra", "yu"],
    "answer": "ra"
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "kana": "り",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["e", "shi", "ri", "ke"],
    "answer": "ri"
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "kana": "る",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["ru", "ko", "e", "so"],
    "answer": "ru"
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "kana": "れ",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["re", "nu", "ya", "n"],
    "answer": "re"
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "kana": "ろ",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["fu", "ro", "ko", "yo"],
    "answer": "ro"
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "kana": "わ",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["ya", "re", "u", "wa"],
    "answer": "wa"
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "kana": "を",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["ni", "shi", "wo", "ro"],
    "answer": "wo"
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "kana": "ん",
    "question": "What is the reading of this character?",
    "options": ["ro", "mo", "e", "n"],
    "answer": "n"
  }
]
